<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shannan's Write-y Things</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/</link><description>Recent content on Shannan's Write-y Things</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2020-2021 Shannan Lekwati ([Source](https://github.com/slekwati/blog.lekwati.com))</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.lekwati.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Victory Dance - 'You are cordially invited'</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap1/</guid><description>Breakfast with the Frasers
When the War was over, my father refused to take down our blackout curtains for ages. Most of the curtains were removed right away, with some women transforming the leftover materials into dresses and skirts as quickly as they could. They heard rumours that the men wanted to burn them in a bonfire, so it was better that they stashed them away safely. That day, everyone had tuned into the radio to listen to Churchill finally announce that the War was over.</description></item><item><title>Victory Dance - Cheek to Cheek</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap6/</guid><description>The music was uptempo and jazzy as we finally reached the floor, my hand in his the entire time. After finding our spot, where the hard wood of the dance floor met with the carpeted area of the rest of the hall, I wrinkled my nose and huffed a small sigh, &amp;ldquo;I think this might be a Charleston?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a Foxtrot,&amp;rdquo; Thomas explained, taking my hands to ready our stance, &amp;ldquo;Less kicks.</description></item><item><title>Victory Dance - Going for a Spin</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap5/</guid><description>My stomach was now happily overly satiated, full with rich gravies from the bacon wrapped chicken roast and the thick, sweet sauce from the sticky toffee pudding. Liz looked like she was ready to bounce off every single surface in the room from all the sugar she had just eaten, having finished Dad&amp;rsquo;s pudding off for him as well as her own.
I sipped at the after dinner coffee, handing over the little packages of shortbread to Louie for his consumption.</description></item><item><title>Victory Dance - How to Make an Entrance</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap3/</guid><description>It was a real rarity for everyone to be stuffed into the car together.
&amp;ldquo;Louie! Stop &amp;ndash; sitting &amp;ndash; on &amp;ndash; my &amp;ndash; dress!&amp;rdquo; Eliza growled, banging her fist against Luis' leg with each word.
&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Ey! I won&amp;rsquo;t have none of dat!&amp;rdquo;
There were reasons for why we were rarely stuffed in the car together. I sighed, wishing I could press my head against the window for some space as Dad trundled the car along the road, but I was forced to take the seat behind Dad&amp;rsquo;s because Luis was so lanky and had to sit behind mum, where her chair was pulled up closer to the dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Victory Dance - Pin-ups and Gossips</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap2/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s it all about, Naaancy?
If the days leading up to invitations being sent out were filled with rumours, then the days after they were received were filled with a heady rush in making sure everything was prepared. New dresses were to be swapped or found or made, make-up was scrounged for or created if you knew how. Of course, the men were all as calm as cucumbers. The most they had to prepare for was lining their stomachs on the night.</description></item><item><title>Victory Dance - Prologue</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-prologue/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-prologue/</guid><description>The war overseas may be over, but the war on our shores has just begun&amp;hellip;
Britain is forever changed and trying to rebuild in the aftermath of WW2. It&amp;rsquo;s a time for celebration of the victory, solemnity for those lost and depending on community now more than ever to thrive in a new global market.
Despite everything against her, Ruth Fraser managed to make a name for herself during the War, even if it meant putting her love life on hold.</description></item><item><title>Victory Dance - Speechless</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/victory-dance-chap4/</guid><description>The Hall was filled with big, round tables each filled with bottles of wine and whisky, little nibbles and a beautiful spray of flowers in the middle, with little decorative flags nestled inside. Music flowed around the room, gently cushioning each table with the comfort that their conversation couldn&amp;rsquo;t be overhead by others. At least, that was the case for all tables but ours.
Though each table was comfortably set for 10 people, ours was overfilled.</description></item><item><title>Heart and Soul</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/heart-and-soul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/heart-and-soul/</guid><description>Cassie Thompson is left with somewhat of a conundrum on her hands when her young son is
too scared to go grocery shopping during the pandemic. Lucky for her, her handsome rouge
of a next door neighbour, Liam, is happy enough to take care of her son for a couple
hours. But it seems like he has an ulterior motive</description></item><item><title>Real Love</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/real-love/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/real-love/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve never been one for soppy romance. I balk at all the Nicholas Sparks books. I can&amp;rsquo;t keep quiet when watching a Rom-Com. They're filled with cliché meet-cutes, predictable misunderstanding and declarations of love.
That&amp;rsquo;s not to say that I don&amp;rsquo;t like love. I love love. I love love when it's stripped down to the bare essentials, when it comes to the quiet displays of care and attention. Now-a-days it&amp;rsquo;s all about being whisked away on surprise, jet-setting adventures by your billionaire boyfriend on your first date or waking up to a room filled with single-stem roses.</description></item><item><title>If/Then</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/if-then/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:17:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/if-then/</guid><description>&lt;p>Anxiety about the following day is keeping Katherine Lawrence awake at night.
A creeping sensation of fear stops her from being able to rest.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What exactly is making her so anxious?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fountain of Youth</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/fountain-of-youth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 21:46:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/fountain-of-youth/</guid><description>&lt;p>Alex and Mary were a globe-trotting power couple in their youth.
Now celebrating their 25th anniversary in Las Vegas, Mary is wondering what might lay ahead for them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This was is an extension of the Chick-lit Flashfiction competition for January 2021&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Friday Night Movie Club</title><link>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/friday-night-movie-club/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lekwati.com/posts/friday-night-movie-club/</guid><description>Friday Nights were made for movies and curling up with a loved one.
But what happens when that love isn&amp;rsquo;t really there anymore?
A short story about lost long-term love and what may be gained instead</description></item></channel></rss>